Guide to the Mary Beth and Richard Hess Technical Manual Collection M1381
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Mary Beth and Richard Hess technical manual collection
1967-2000
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Hess, Mary Beth
Hess, Richard L.
Ampex Corporation
Hewlett-Packard Company
Grass Valley Group
M1381
35 Linear Feet (82 boxes)
Contains technical user manuals for products built and sold by the Ampex Corporation, Grass Valley Group, Hewlett-Packard Corporation and other technology firms. Includes manuals, bulletins, catalogs, brochures, and schematics largely concerning the use, maintenance and repair of audiovisual equipment. The manuals have been removed from their original binders, however a representative sampling of binder graphics has been retained.
Related Materials
Stanford University Special Collections holds the Grass Valley Group, Inc.: publications, 1999-2002, M1604 (donated by Richard Hess) as well as the Ampex Corporation Records, M1230. The Archive of Recorded Sound holds the Richard Hess Mullin-Palmer Tape Restoration Project Collection, ARS.0035 [audio transfers assembled by Hess).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mary Beth and Richard L. Hess, 2003 & 2015. Accession # 2003-153, 2015-041.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical / Historical
Mary Beth and Richard Hess are a married couple that lived in Glendale, California at the time of donation while Richard was employed by National TeleConsultants LLC. In addition to consulting, Richard has worked extensively in audio preservation and owns an audio-related patent. Mary Beth has worked at IBM, in real estate, and with religious and cultural organizations.
Since focusing on audio preservation Richard has contributed significantly to the field of sound recording preservation, especially magnetic media preservation. He has shared his audio expertise through articles and has presented at national conferences for organizations ranging from the Audio Engineering Society to the Association for Recorded Sound Collections. Richard holds U.S. patent 3784746.
Technical manuals; Science -- History.; Audio-visual materials; Hess, Mary Beth; Hess, Richard L.; Ampex Corporation; Hewlett-Packard Company; Grass Valley Group
- Series 1: Ampex manuals, schematics, brochures, and bulletins
  - 30960 circuitry for audio recorder/reproducers, electronics assembly, 1967 October (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Brochures including ADO, ACE, TBC, VPR and Betacam products, 1980-1990 (Box 80, Folders 1-4)
  - 4000 series production switcher information, installation, and operation; catalog number 1809376-01, 1979 November (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 4100MC-4 master control video switcher service data package (schematics); catalog number 1809600-02, 1984 July (Box 17, Folders 1-2)
  - ACE ampex computerized editor parts list and schematics volume 1; catalog number 1809661-01, 1985 April (Box 6, Folders 5-6)
  - ACE ampex computerized editor parts list and schematics volume 2; catalog number 1809662-01, 1985 April (Box 7, Folders 1-2)
  - ACE ampex computerized editor installation and routine maintenance; catalog number 1809665-01, 1985 March (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ACR-25 automatic videocassette recorder/reproducer control logic guide; catalog number 1809158-01, 1973 December (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ACR-25 automatic video cassette recorder/reproducer theory of operation; catalog number 1809137-01, 1974 July (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ACR-25 automatic video cassette recorder/reproducer audio and cue system theory of operation; catalog number 1809145-01, 1972 November (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ACR-25 automatic videocassette recorder/reproducer system logic and theory of operation; catalog number 1809141-01, 1976 May (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ACR-25B automatic video cassette recorder/reproducer audio and cue system operation; catalog number 1809327-01, 1978 March (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ADO ampex digital objects product description; catalog number 1809538-02, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ADO ampex digital optics operator's guide; catalog number 1809551-01, 1982 December (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ADO ampex digital optics service; catalog number 1809550-03, 1983 November (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ADO ampex digital optics parts list and schematics volume 1; catalog number 1809622-05, 1985 March (Box 7, Folders 3-4)
  - ADO ampex digital optics parts list and schematics volume 2; catalog number 1809623-05, 1985 March (Box 8, Folders 1-2)
  - ADO-2000 ampex digital optics operators guide; catalog number 1809671-02, 1985 August (Box 5, Folders 8)
  - ADO-2000 ampex digital optics service manual NTSC/PAL; catalog number 1809695-01, 1985 December (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - AG-440 audio recorder/reproducer selected schematics; catalog number 4890301-01, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - AVA-3 video art system operation; catalog number 1809673-02, 1987 December (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - AVA-3 video art system service; catalog number 1809674-04, 1988 January (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - AVC series production video switchers service; catalog number 1809601-02, 1984 August (Box 3, Folders 3-4)
  - AVC production video switchers general information, installation, and operation; catalog number 1809599-02, 1984 January (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AVC series universal panel controller service; catalog number 1809624-01, 1983 December (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AVC production video switchers general information, installation, and operation; catalog number 1809599-03, 1985 September (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AVC series audio system service manual volume 1 general information, installation, and operation; catalog number 1809651-02, 1986 January (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - AVR-1 videotape recorder operators handbook; catalog number 1809030-10, 1971 December (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - AVR-1 videotape recorder operation and maintenance volume 1; catalog number 1809009-03, 1973 July (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
  - AVR-1 videotape recorder operation and maintenance volume 2; catalog number 1809009-03, 1973 July (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - AVR-1 videotape recorder operation and maintenance volume 3; catalog number 1809009-03, 1974 April (Box 14, Folders 1-2)
    - AVR-1 videotape recorder operation and maintenance volume 4; catalog number 1809009-03, 1973 July (Box 15, Folders 1-2)
  - AVR-1 editec accessory operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809189-01, 1975 February (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - AVR-1 videotape recorder operation and maintenance volume 5; catalog number 1809009-03, 1973 July (Box 15, Folders 3-4)
  - AVR-2 video tape recorder theory of operation; catalog number 1809179-01, 1977 November (Box 9, Folders 1-2)
  - AVR-2 EC-2 edit controller and edit interface kit operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809396-01, 1979 February (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AVR-3 videotape recorder/reproducer parts lists and schematics volume 1; catalog number 1809291-01, 1977 April (Box 9, Folders 3-4)
  - AVR-3 videotape recorder/reproducer parts lists and schematics volume 2; catalog number 1809292-01, 1977 April (Box 10, Folders 1-2)
  - BCC-20 broadcast color camera advance information; catalog number 1809467-01, 1980 August (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ESS-3 electronic still store installation and routine maintenance; catalog number 1809649-01, 1985 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - HPE-1 helical production editor American Broadcasting Companies operating procedures, 1980 September (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ESS-2 digital video production system advance information parts list and schematics volume 2; catalog number 1809344-01, 1977 January (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ESS-2 digital video production system advance information operation and schematics volume 1; catalog number 1809344-01, 1979 March (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - ESS-3 graphic composition and storage system service; catalog number 1809653-02, 1988 April (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ESS-3 electronic Still Store operating instructions; catalog number 1809638-01, 1985 June (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - ESS-5 and ESS-5G electronic still store service; catalog number 1809796-01, 1987 December (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ESS-5 electronic still store operation; catalog number 1809795-01, 1987 July (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - HPE-1 helical production editor installation and operation 1981 revision; catalog number 1809436-02, 1981 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - HPE series helical production editor parts list and schematics; catalog number 1809604-01, 1983 March (Box 17, Folders 3)
  - MM-1200 (including MM-1100 and AG-440C) pick-up recording accessory operation and maintenance; catalog number 4890408-01, 1976 December (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - MM-1200 multichannel recorder reproducer operation and maintenance; catalog number 4890400-02, 1977 October (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - TBC-2 digital time base corrector NTSC service data package; catalog number 1809371-01, 1978 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - TBC-2 digital time base corrector NTSC parts list and schematics; catalog number 1809381-01, 1978 December (Box 5, Folders 9)
  - TBC-2 digital time base corrector PAL/SECAM installation, operation, theory of operation, and schematics; catalog number 1809403-01, 1979 March (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - TBC-2B digital time-based corrector NTSC description and maintenance; catalog 1809474-01, 1981 August (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - TBC-7 digital time base corrector parts list and schematics; catalog number 1520475-01, 1987 November (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - TBC-7 digital time base corrector installation and operation; catalog number 1520479-01, 1987 November (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - TBC-7 digital time base corrector service; catalog number 1520480-01, 1988 February (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - TBC-80 time base corrector NTSC schematics, 1982 June (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - VPR-2 video production recorder parts list and schematics; catalog number 1809384-01, 1979 February (Box 8, Folders 4-5)
  - VPR-1 video production recorder service data package; catalog number 1809277-01, 1977 April (Box 18, Folders 5)
  - VPR-1 video production recorder maintenance; catalog number 1809249-01, 1978 March (Box 18, Folders 3-4)
  - VPR-2 video production recorder American Broadcasting Companies operating procedures, 1979 July (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - VPR-2 video production recorder service data package; catalog number 1809370-01, 1979 October (Box 6, Folders 1-2)
  - VPR-2 video production recorder American Broadcasting Companies machine modifications including some schematics, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - VPR-2B video production recorder installation and operation; catalog number 1809519-01, 1981 July (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - VPR-2B video production recorder theory and maintenance; catalog number 1809477-01, 1981 August (Box 5, Folders 6-7)
  - VPR-3 video production recorder service manual; catalog number 1809594-02, 1985 August (Box 6, Folders 3-4)
  - VPR-3 video production recorder NTSC schematics, 1980's (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - VPR-6 video production recorder service; catalog number 1809634-04, 1988 February (Box 2, Folders 3-4)
  - VPR-6 video production recorder installation and routine maintenance; catalog number 1809648-02, 1985 July (Box 2, Folders 5)
  - VPR-6 video production recorder operating instructions; catalog number 1809595-03, 1987 September (Box 3, Folders 1)
  - VPR-80 and TBC-80 video production recorder installation and operation; catalog number 1809546-01, 1983 January (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - VPR-80 schematics, 1980's (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - VRC-2 video tape recorder remote controller installation and operation; catalog number 1809669-01, 1985 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Auto-chroma accessory kit operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809050-01, 1971 December (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Betacam part number cross-reference; catalog number 1809783-01, 1986 November (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Field engineering bulletins related to VPR-6 video tape recorder, AVR-2 video tape recorder, TBC-80 time base corrector, and AVC switcher, 1978-1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tracking accessory kit operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809054-01, 1971 December (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Universal color processor accessory kit operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809047-01, 1971 August (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Velocity compensator accessory kit operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809048-01, 1971 September (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vertical interval test signal processor accessory kit operation and maintenance; catalog number 1809055-01, 1971 December (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Series 2: Grass Valley Group manuals, schematics, and bulletins
  - 10-XL series maintenance, 1988 December (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 300-3A/B instruction volume 1 of 7, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ten-20-20-ten compact routing systems description, installation, system control, maintenance, parts list, and drawings, 1988 January (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Model 100 video switcher service volume 1, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 300-3A/B instruction volume 2 of 7, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 300-3A/B instruction volume 3 of 7, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 300-3A/B instruction volume 4 of 7, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 300-3A/B instruction volume 5 of 7, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 300-3A/B instruction volume 6 of 7, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 900 series tray and model 900 dual power supply description and schematics, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 901 video distribution amplifier operating, 1976, November (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 903N video distribution amplifier instructions, 1976, December (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 907 distribution amplifier drawings, 1977, August (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 908 color black generator operating, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 910 pulse distribution amplifier instruction, 1977, July (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 910 pulse distribution amplifier instruction, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 911 pulse fanout amplifier, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 911 pulse fanout amplifier instruction, 1976, July (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 940B video processor instruction, 1977, October (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 950 sync generator instruction, 1976, Decemeber (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 955 3.58 MHz oscillator an color lock operating, 1977, August (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 961 synac instruction, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 962 color lock operating, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 1 of 3, set 1, 1980's (Box 19, Folders 1-2)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 1 of 3, set 2, 1980's (Box 20, Folders 1-2)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 2 of 3, set 2, 1980's (Box 20, Folders 3-4)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 2 of 3, set 1, 1980's (Box 19, Folders 3-4)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 2 of 3, set 3, 1980's (Box 21, Folders 1-2)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 3 of 3, set 1, 1980's (Box 19, Folders 5-6)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 3 of 3, set 2, 1980's (Box 20, Folders 5-6)
  - 1600-1X series equipment manuals volume 3 of 3, set 3, 1980's (Box 21, Folders 3-4)
  - 1600-2V Instruction volume 2 of 3, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1600-2V Instruction volume 3 of 3, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1600-3G/7G Instruction volume 1 of 3, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1600-3G/7G Instruction volume 2 of 3, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1600-3G/7G Instruction volume 3 of 3, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1600-7K Instruction volume 3, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1600-7K instruction volume 4, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Audio e-mem instruction, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 3240 video processing amplifier instruction, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folders 3-4)
  - 3240 video processing amplifier (NTSC) instruction, 1983 October (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 3280 Four channel multiplex system instruction, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 3400 utility video distribution amplifier instruction, 1983 October (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 3401V video distribution amplifier instruciton, 1983 October (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 8465 drawings (schematics), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 8500 series video/pulse distribution amplifier instruction, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 8500 series video/pulse distribution amplifier instruction, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 8500 series video/pulse distribution amplifier instruction, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 8550 series audio distribution amplifier instruction, 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - MK II DVE (NTSC) digital video effects system instruction volume 1, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - AMX-100 audio mixer service, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - MK II DVE (NTSC) digital video effects system instruction volume 2, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - CV-20 series analog component video products instruction, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Emphasys (NTSC) digital encode system operators, 1990 October (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Kadenza DPP-1 digital picture processing system operator, 1988 December (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Max series user, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folders 5-6)
  - Super edit video tape editor version 4.16 software update documentation (includes version 4.1 and 4.14 documentation), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 8501/8801 series video distribution amplifier installation and service, 1992 August (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 8520 pulse distribution amplifier description and adjustment, 1992 September (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Kadenza drawings/parts lists, 1989 March (Box 82)
  - Kadenza drawings package, 1988 December (Box 82)
  - Integrated machine control drawings package, 1986 (Box 82)
  - VPE 151 video production editor drawings package, 1988 (Box 82)
- Series 3: Miscellaneous manuals, catalogs, schematics, brochures, and bulletins
  - 360 systems permanent playback series 4000 digital audio message system operator, 1986-1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 3M D-8800 graphics systems installation and operation volume 1 including service update no.2; catalog number 80-9403-1665-1, 1981 August (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - 3M scotch videodiscs premastering/post production procedures, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - ADDA corporation models 150C, 200C, and 750C electronic still processor operators; catalog number 70108, 1982 July (Box 33, Folders 1-2)
  - Adam Smith inc. Model 2600 SY tape synchronizer instructions and schematics, 1984 November (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Adam Smith inc. TS 650B tape synchronizer instruction, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - ADC telecommunications QCP installation; catalog number 4-26644-1000, 1991 October (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - ADDA corporation VW-2 time base corrector operation and mainetnance; catalog number 70080, 1981 July (Box 32, Folders 10-11)
  - ADM technology inc. 1203 panel layout schematic; drawing number 105162, 1984 March (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - ADM technology inc. Radio Free Europe console diagrams, 1985 September (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - ADM technology inc. VP series schematics, 1984 August (Box 39, Folders 1-2)
  - ADM technology inc. M-1580 effects filter schematic; drawing number 104293, 1985 August (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - ADM technology inc. V0803, V1203, and V1603 system schematic; drawing number 105171, 1984 August (Box oversized, Folder 6)
  - ADM technology inc. ST100 II, 160 II, 200II, 240 II series consoles customer documentation package, 1985 June (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ADM technology inc. VO803, 1203, 1603-001 system schematic, 1983 July (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - AKG BX 20E reverberation unit service manual, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Altec 1628A automatic microphone mixer operation, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Auburn instruments MC/1 technical, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Audio precision testing manuals and newsletters, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Audio precision System One software version 2.00A twelfth revision user, 1989 Decemeber (Box 39, Folders 3-4)
  - Barco CTVM2-series NTSC precision colour monitor, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - BBC Brown, Boveri, and Company transmitter brochures (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - BBC TV master sound control vehicle brochure, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - B and B systems AM-3B phase monitor operation and maintenance, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Bell and Howell TCG-3000 graphics system compositor 1 operation and technical, 1978 October (Box 34, Folders 1-2)
  - BC engineering AC 400 audio control device oeprators, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Bosch FGS-4000 graphics system technical; catalog number 04-028595-001 Rev.B, 1985 January (Box 34, Folders 3-4)
  - Bosch Bosch FGS-4000 graphics system schematics; catalog number 04-028595-001 Rev.B, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folders 1-2)
  - Broadcast technology inc. 3000 system brochure, 1984 November (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Broadcast technology inc. AB 3104 parts list and schematic, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Broadcast technology inc. PS3400 parts list and schematic, 1984 November (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Brüel and Kjær miscellaneous brouchures, 1976-1985 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Brüel and Kjær short form catalogs, 1985-1988 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Brüel and Kjær technical reviews 1972, 1973, 1978, 1984, 1985, 1986, 1987, and 1988, 1972-1988 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Channelmatic, inc. Digital code generator schematic, 1983 Feruary (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Chyron telesystems IIIB operating; catalog number A-200-0038, 1976 February (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Cinetronics EDM-1 Computer controlled editing system diagnostic; catalog number 1809298-01, 1977 July (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Cinetronics EDM-1 Computer controlled editing system, system manual, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Cohu 8000 and 8120 Camera installation, operation, and maintenance; catalog number 6X-774, 1982 September (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Digital Equipment Corporation basic plus language, 1975 July (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Comdial 824 electronic key system installation, programming, and maintenance, 1985 June (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Comdial 308 electronic key system installation, programming, and maintenance, 1985 April (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Comdial 616 electronic key system installation, programming, and maintenance, 1985 June (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Computer magnetics corp fact sheets, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Conex UM-33 cue amp, 1982 January (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Conrac model 6122 and 6142 Master Color Picture Monitors installation, operation, and maintenance, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Convergence corporation 200 series quick reference guide, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Control video corporation intelligent controller manual, 1982 March (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Cox type 253 Secam coder, 1978 May (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Dantel master catalog volume 2 40000 series, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folders 10-11)
  - Continental electronics catalogs, 1986-1988 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Crown D-75 power amplifier owners, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Dantel master catalog volume 1 90000 series, 1982-1985 (Box 37, Folders 2-3)
  - Datatron 5650-178 Vanguard schematic manual, 1979-1982 (Box 82)
  - Datatron Vanguard operating manual rev. a with addendum; catalog number 949940, 1981-1983 (Box 37, Folders 4-5)
  - Dictaphone 5600 veritrac sl preliminary service manual, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Digital video systems B-Mac commercial decoder series 9700, 525 line models operators issue 3; catalog number 707-200, 1985 November (Box 37, Folders 6)
  - Digital video systems B-Mac commercial decoder BD-525/I models operators issue 1; catalog number 707-093, 1985 November (Box 37, Folders 7)
  - Digital video systems B-Mac commercial decoder BD-525/I models operators issue 1; catalog number 707-214, 1985 November (Box 37, Folders 8)
  - Dubner computer systems CBG-2 installation and maintenance, 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folders 1-3)
  - Dolby system 334 type B noise reduction broadcast unit operation, installation and schematic, 1971-1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Dolby system 361 type A noise reduction system operation, service, and schematics, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Dubner computer systems CBG-2 technical, 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folders 4-5)
  - Eigen video disc recorders 16-10, 16-20, 17-10, and 17-20 operating and service, 1982 November (Box 38, Folder 9)